<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to Sahil&#39;s Personal Site :)</title>
    <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Welcome to Sahil&#39;s Personal Site :)</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 00:02:34 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://acerrimus.srht.site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Levels Draft</title>
      <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/levels-draft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 00:02:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/levels-draft/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;on-the-levels-to-reality&#34;&gt;On the levels to reality.&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ken Wilbur talks about Levels of being in his books on Integral Theory. I want to take my time to reflect on them, and add my own touches, in the hopes it makes for a pleasant and insightful read.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We live ours lives spending different amounts of time at different ‘levels’ of being, which can be labeled in any number of ways, but Ken Wilbur labels them very helpfully as colours.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I guess I&#39;m not special</title>
      <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/notspecial/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 01:13:28 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/notspecial/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Everything I’ve been doing has been simply for the sake of convincing myself that I matter, that I’m somehow special and different, inherently, not in the modern &amp;rsquo;everyone is unique and special&amp;rsquo; sense. But I’m not. I’m not smart enough to breeze through everything effortlessly like Will Hunting. I’m not a fictional character capable of inventing anything. I don’t have infinite will power at any given moment, and even if I was all of those, it probably still wouldn’t be enough. Not against the cold indifference of the abyss, who&amp;rsquo;s chilling presence is felt even by super heroes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Case Study&#39; on how I use AI as an Engineering Student</title>
      <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/studentcasestudy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 00:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/studentcasestudy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;student-case-study-on-leveraging-ai-effectively-for-education&#34;&gt;Student Case Study on Leveraging AI effectively for education.&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As an Engineering student on a Level 3 BTEC, a significant portion of my studies involves processing, understanding, and writing text containing engineering insights and data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The biggest processes involved in my studies at the moment are the following:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Drafting content for assignments&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Extracting information from specific sources&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Quickly researching specific data and sources.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;drafting-templates-for-my-assignments&#34;&gt;Drafting templates for my assignments&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The majority of my time is spent writing or adjusting assignments. This is admittedly not ideal, as part of an engineering student’s education is getting a profound and nuanced understanding of the underlying engineering and scientific principles, not creating well-written essays.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Business</title>
      <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/forbusiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 00:09:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/forbusiness/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-me&#34;&gt;About Me&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Sahil. I&amp;rsquo;m an 18-year-old Engineering Student and future Tech Founder from England, with a goal of designing and implementing technology that drives human progress to unpresidented achievements. I&amp;rsquo;m currently completing my Engineering BTEC (predicted D*DD), but most of my learning happens outside the classroom, independently.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;technical-skills&#34;&gt;Technical Skills&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Python (CS50p certified)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;HTML/CSS&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;SQL/Databases&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Linux CLI navigation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Programming Microcontrollers&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;CAD design&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Currently learning: JavaScript &amp;amp; Node.js&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;professional-experience&#34;&gt;Professional Experience&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI Model Training for Outlier| Contract Work&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lucid</title>
      <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/lucid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 02:59:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/lucid/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Maybe there&amp;rsquo;s a different pursuit of perfection.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s just being. Without individuality.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Individuality is a sort of fever dream I guess.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are everything and nothingness all at once, and then we part from ourselves to experience it all from an &amp;lsquo;individual&amp;rsquo; perspective&amp;hellip; Only to inevitably return to oneness.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is no harm in this, infact harm isn&amp;rsquo;t even real.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Everything just is.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m the universe cutting off a piece of itself just to appreciate its own beauty&amp;hellip; In other words&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notes on Arcane (raw)</title>
      <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/arcane-raw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 02:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/arcane-raw/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Perfection brings nothing. Only the end of pursuit&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Or something like that, holy fuck that was important.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What an incredible message.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Viktor remains my favourite for his pursuit of perfection and the fact that he&amp;rsquo;s responsible for literally everything. Next is probably powder and echo.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Powder is second, echo last.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Powder and Echos romance was really touching, it made me feel something.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s the dream for me, what powder and echo had. Is it attainable? Is it realistic?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to never drop a hobby after 2 weeks again (How to Go from Thinker to Doer)</title>
      <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/thinkervsdoer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:06:46 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/thinkervsdoer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;doing-is-a-trait-you-can-level-up&#34;&gt;‘Doing’ is a trait you can level up.&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Something I&amp;rsquo;ve always struggled with is sticking to my interests, there are so many random niche things I&amp;rsquo;ve been exposed to, gotten interested about for a week or 2, but then ended up dropping it cause I either just forget about it or lose interest, or simply never seem to &amp;lsquo;adopt&amp;rsquo; it as a part of my life. This applies not only to hobbies, but ideas and philosophies and frameworks too. How many times have we been exposed to an excellent idea that would improve our lives immensely if integrated, only to drop it before it even gets a chance to flourish and yield benefits?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 13:35:54 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/books/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve read quite a few, but these are some of my favourites I read again and again.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;deep-work---cal-newport&#34;&gt;Deep Work - Cal Newport&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rating: 9/10&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why:&lt;/strong&gt; Deep work is a vital book for getting more flow in your life, Which could be argued is basically one of the main points of existence as a human. Your ability to get deep work done in one of the biggest factors in just how much progress you make in any sort of knowledge work, and arguably beyond it too. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a student, programmer, entrepreneur, marketer, whatever, this book will help you massivey in getting more out of your work day, as well as learning new skills quicker.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coaches, not Clients: A guide to reading effectively.</title>
      <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/coachesnotclients/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 13:22:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/coachesnotclients/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;context&#34;&gt;Context&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I was reading Deep Work by Cal Newport while simultaneously processing one of the most important issues I’ve been having in my life: I seem to know exactly what to do and when to do it, I know so many techniques and philosophies, and I’m excellent and giving advice to others (if I do say so myself) on precisely what they need to do right now, and do so with certainty that if they followed it exactly, they’d succeed&amp;hellip; but then why haven&amp;rsquo;t I succeeded to the extent I would like to already?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explanation of the Mess</title>
      <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/explanation-of-the-mess/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 16:56:58 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/explanation-of-the-mess/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;wtf-is-going-on-sahil&#34;&gt;Wtf is going on Sahil?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m trying to sub categorise my blogs into guides - personal posts - and other forms, but strugglignto figure it all out,that&amp;rsquo;s why my site is all over the place. I don&amp;rsquo;t care about making mistakes rn, or doing things ineffectively, I&amp;rsquo;m just playing around to wrap my head around things.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That being said, please excuse any grammatical, logical, structural, philosophical, or whatever the fuck else kinda mistakes, I&amp;rsquo;m still learning and trying to show the process :)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:18:05 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;me&#34;&gt;Me&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m Sahil, at the time of writing I am &lt;del&gt;17&lt;/del&gt; 18 years old and live in England.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;passions&#34;&gt;Passions&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My biggest passion is simply being at the vanguard of human development in some shape or form.&#xA;My dream is to run companies with trillion dollar valuation that genuinely change the world&#xA;for the better, while working towards the goal of bringing my space travel dreams to life.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are a lot of things I enjoy doing and would love to imagine I&amp;rsquo;m good at,&#xA;but my main interests at the moment are:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 13:45:36 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/introduction/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;hi-im-sahil&#34;&gt;Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Sahil!&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my blog, I don&amp;rsquo;t really know what exactly it&amp;rsquo;s for at the time of writing, but it seemed like a good idea, so here we are.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now that I think about it, this page is kinda reundant cause all my info is on me about page so uhhh&amp;hellip; go check that out &lt;a href=&#34;https://acerrimus.srht.site/about/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; lol.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/neverendingparty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/neverendingparty/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s 16:00 and I woke up around about 15:00 after a terrible night of procrastination and existential dread, and the first thing I did was get up and go over to my already se up calculus books, and just started reading and doing practice questions. My dopamine levels feel absolutely perfect right now, they&amp;rsquo;re not euphoric or anything, but they feel extremely stable and sufficient.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I noticed that as soon as I was done, I got a very minor suggestion in my mind to check my phone now, and I noticed the immediate dopamine prediction that occured and how it would completely throw this balance away no matter what. Phone usage seems to invariably throw away my balance, more specifically, social phone usage, and since my phone is primarily a means of connecting with other people, it is almost diretly associated with social usage.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/special/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/special/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/wtf-am-i-doing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/wtf-am-i-doing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you found my ideas interesting, and would like to chat, feel free to contact me through any of the following:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Personal email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sahilsingh.contact@gmail.com&#34;&gt;sahilsingh.contact@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Discord: Acerrimus&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Instagram (Deactivated 90% of the time): &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.instagram.com/ig_sxhil&#34;&gt;ig_sxhil (Main account)&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.instagram.com/sahil_secondaccount/&#34;&gt;My alt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Etc</title>
      <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/etc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/etc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This page contains an assortment of various links, that I find interesting or otherwise deem worth sharing. The sorting order of anything here is completely arbitrary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you have a blog of your own, feel free to send me a link, I’d love to check it out.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;friends&#34;&gt;Friends:&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ash.fail&#34;&gt;ash.fail&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ash has been a huge help while I&amp;rsquo;m still in training wheels on everything CS, and is the inspiration for this blog, should definitely go check him out.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
