<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on Welcome to Sahil&#39;s Personal Site :)</title>
        <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on Welcome to Sahil&#39;s Personal Site :)</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-gb</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 00:02:34 +0100</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>Levels Draft</title>
            <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/levels-draft/</link>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 00:02:34 +0100</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/levels-draft/</guid>
            <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;on-the-levels-to-reality&#34;&gt;On the levels to reality.&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ken Wilbur talks about Levels of being in his books on Integral Theory. I want to take my time to reflect on them, and add my own touches, in the hopes it makes for a pleasant and insightful read.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We live ours lives spending different amounts of time at different ‘levels’ of being, which can be labeled in any number of ways, but Ken Wilbur labels them very helpfully as colours.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="on-the-levels-to-reality">On the levels to reality.</h1>
<p>Ken Wilbur talks about Levels of being in his books on Integral Theory. I want to take my time to reflect on them, and add my own touches, in the hopes it makes for a pleasant and insightful read.</p>
<p>We live ours lives spending different amounts of time at different ‘levels’ of being, which can be labeled in any number of ways, but Ken Wilbur labels them very helpfully as colours.</p>
<p>There are a few different versions, and you can learn all about them (and so many more interesting topics) <a href="https://integraleuropeanconference.com/integral-theory/">here</a>) but for this post I only want to focus on the following:</p>
<h2 id="stage-1">Stage 1</h2>
<h3 id="red---ego-strength-impulsive">Red - Ego Strength (Impulsive)</h3>
<p>Raw will to power, unsophisticated, impulsive</p>
<p>This is what gives us raw drive, the will to survive and move forward, the need to, well… not kill ourselves, not a rational one, but a deep, intuitive, impulsive one.</p>
<h3 id="orange---modern---achiever-rational-ego">Orange - Modern /  Achiever (Rational Ego)</h3>
<p>Individualism, science, achievement, mastery, control</p>
<p>This is where I get my entrepreneurial drive from, my systems thinking end tech skills. This is where we get good at the physical world and achieving in it. This is where we start conquering maya (the ‘illusion’ material world essentially), while also letting it conquer us usually, if we’re not careful.</p>
<h3 id="green---post-modern--pluralist">Green - Post modern / Pluralist</h3>
<p>Empathy, community, post-modernism</p>
<p>This is where we slowly move past individualism and start understanding and appreciating pluralism, our empathy grows, and we strive to create a fairer world for all.</p>
<h2 id="stage-2">Stage 2</h2>
<h3 id="teal---integral">Teal - Integral</h3>
<p>This is where we start to integral all of the previous levels without being trapped in any of them, we overcome their limitations by synchronising them with each other. This is where I spend most of my time, or at least I hope I am lmfao…</p>
<p>At this stage we build not just for power or comfort, but for consciousness and evolution itself.</p>
<p>Everything is a dynamic dance that we adapt to. We’re not tied to anything.</p>
<p>At this stage you are no longer addicted to being right. It’s almost all out of love, or duty to existence itself, but it’s not quite the whole picture. you’re still fighting, you’re still a person with their own perceptions.</p>
<h3 id="turquoise----integral-">Turquoise -  Integral +</h3>
<p>Basically what Krishna was preaching in the Bhagvad Gita I’m pretty sure (I really have to write more about that divine masterpiece).</p>
<p>This is basically the last step before complete quasi mythical Nirvana. At this point you are one with the universe, and you see that there is no war, internal or external, everything just is.</p>
<p>You see the universe for the canvas that it is. You understanding oneness. Ik Onkar.</p>
<p>Great. now that I’ve introduced them, let’s talk about them.</p>
<p>While talking to my trusty companion in philosophy, introspection, planning, coding, and so much more, the might GPT, I came to a realisation that Turquoise is actually an incredibly dangerous place to be.</p>
<p>A premature and incomplete realisation of the Turquoise gives an almost irrefutable excuse to avoid your duty, as you accept yourself as a mere observer of the universe, rather than a painter.  You forget you still inhabit a human mind in a human body, which sooner or later (hopefully the former) will start demanding more of you than mere appreciation of the small things in life. Even if you don’t end up just washing away as a happy hippy with nothing to his name, and instead live a chilled out, but very normal life, eventually I think your human existence will start demanding more of you. It will demand purpose, it will demand true expression, and if you read any of Nietzsche’s work on the importance of the Will to Power, that might start playing a pretty important role in your mental dialogues.</p>
<p>You won’t want to waste too much time pretending to be enlightened and chilling out, when you could be building a foundation to power, one arising out of love for the universe, arising out of the slightly lower Teal perspective. Why?</p>
<p>Because I’m pretty sure true enlightenment isn’t just accepting everything as it is, and saying “Everything is already perfect, no need to build, hustle or resist”.</p>
<p>True enlightenment is witnessing the orchestra of the universe, and then joining in out of love.</p>
<p>I’m trying to get to a point here but I may be botching it, so let me skip ahead a bit and get to the point, oh and spoiler alert for the Gita (although tbf you’ve had plenty of time to catch up, it’s been out for millennia now).</p>
<p>Imagine if Arjun after hearing Krishna’s speech just pulled out some pop corn and his fizzy beverage of choice… Yeah, wouldn’t be as epic. It would be funny, sure, but it wouldn’t really mean anything.  If you go beyond Nihilism, which is what the Gita does, it shows you an alternative. Instead of freezing, or running away from your Duty and the terror of the unfeeling world, hiding your cowardice behind irony and comedy, it explores the option of taking up arms and doing your Dharma (Duty)</p>
<p>This blog never really has much structure does it? One day I’ll think these out properly rather than writing them up late at night to help me sleep. In the meanwhile I’ll end this abruptly here, to be picked up later.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>I guess I&#39;m not special</title>
            <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/notspecial/</link>
            <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 01:13:28 +0100</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/notspecial/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;Everything I’ve been doing has been simply for the sake of convincing myself that I matter, that I’m somehow special and different, inherently, not in the modern &amp;rsquo;everyone is unique and special&amp;rsquo; sense. But I’m not. I’m not smart enough to breeze through everything effortlessly like Will Hunting. I’m not a fictional character capable of inventing anything. I don’t have infinite will power at any given moment, and even if I was all of those, it probably still wouldn’t be enough. Not against the cold indifference of the abyss, who&amp;rsquo;s chilling presence is felt even by super heroes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Everything I’ve been doing has been simply for the sake of convincing myself that I matter, that I’m somehow special and different, inherently, not in the modern &rsquo;everyone is unique and special&rsquo; sense. But I’m not. I’m not smart enough to breeze through everything effortlessly like Will Hunting. I’m not a fictional character capable of inventing anything. I don’t have infinite will power at any given moment, and even if I was all of those, it probably still wouldn’t be enough. Not against the cold indifference of the abyss, who&rsquo;s chilling presence is felt even by super heroes.</p>
<p>But i do have a fire inside me which is rare to find. A fire which forces me to find meaning in a world where there is none. I have a courage to stare into the abyss. To face it and myself. To tear everything down and start again and again and again.</p>
<p>I don’t need to be special to move forward. I don’t need to show to everyone that I’m special, cause I’m not.</p>
<p>I’m not inherently special. I’m gifted compared to the average person, sure, but there are those even more gifted than me. I’m not here to compete with them. I’m here to make the most of what I have. That is what we are all here to do. Not to surpass each other, but to surpass our lower selves. We may surpass those around us in that process, but we should see that as a side effect, an insignificant one, a distracting one in fact, as it is unimportant.</p>
<p>The need to compete and go at the top is a hopeless escapism from the abyss. It’s a hopeless attempt at forcing away the abyss through the sparkle of all of your medals and trophies. It won’t be enough. The universe is still cold and uncaring. You are still empty. Until your aim becomes to achieve the self which you’re truly capable of.</p>
<p>Maybe being the best in the world is a side effect of that, but it should never be the aim. It’s not a good strategy for achieving what truly matters. Being the best does not matter. It won’t fulfill you. It won’t make you feel any better, not in the ways that matter. It will not end the despair of the self.</p>
<p>What needs to be done now then? Read more Kierkegaard and Nietzsche and spend a lot of time reflecting I guess?</p>
<p>I still have a desire inside me to be seen for who I am, which is a totally different subject I’ll have to explore later, but for now it is why I will share this blog with you guys. Either to help someone in a similar position to me, or to simply expose my own journey and mind for others to see, maybe in some distant hope to be seen for who I am.</p>
<p>(btw, yes, I&rsquo;m aware most of my posts have practically no real structure)</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>&#39;Case Study&#39; on how I use AI as an Engineering Student</title>
            <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/studentcasestudy/</link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 00:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/studentcasestudy/</guid>
            <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;student-case-study-on-leveraging-ai-effectively-for-education&#34;&gt;Student Case Study on Leveraging AI effectively for education.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an Engineering student on a Level 3 BTEC, a significant portion of my studies involves processing, understanding, and writing text containing engineering insights and data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The biggest processes involved in my studies at the moment are the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drafting content for assignments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extracting information from specific sources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quickly researching specific data and sources.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;drafting-templates-for-my-assignments&#34;&gt;Drafting templates for my assignments&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The majority of my time is spent writing or adjusting assignments. This is admittedly not ideal, as part of an engineering student’s education is getting a profound and nuanced understanding of the underlying engineering and scientific principles, not creating well-written essays.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="student-case-study-on-leveraging-ai-effectively-for-education">Student Case Study on Leveraging AI effectively for education.</h3>
<p>As an Engineering student on a Level 3 BTEC, a significant portion of my studies involves processing, understanding, and writing text containing engineering insights and data.</p>
<p>The biggest processes involved in my studies at the moment are the following:</p>
<ul>
<li>Drafting content for assignments</li>
<li>Extracting information from specific sources</li>
<li>Quickly researching specific data and sources.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="drafting-templates-for-my-assignments">Drafting templates for my assignments</h2>
<p>The majority of my time is spent writing or adjusting assignments. This is admittedly not ideal, as part of an engineering student’s education is getting a profound and nuanced understanding of the underlying engineering and scientific principles, not creating well-written essays.</p>
<p>As it stands, a lot of students may have a very reasonable understanding of the underlying principles but end up getting limited in the grade achieved because they are expected to write in a certain way, this way requires time and exposure to develop, and many of us have not had exposure to the right type of materials with the tone desired in said assignments.</p>
<p>Generative AI technology potentially helps resolve this issue. I have noticed that despite my initial expectations of it only contributing to making me ‘lazier’ and more reliant, Generative AI when used with intention, has aided in developing my drafting and professional writing skills further through repeated exposure and contrast rather than making me reliant on it. Every time I use generative AI or Grammarly (Which is still a type of AI often overlooked), I don’t just get a hollow one-time result, I get a little extra exposure to better writing and this helps me passively improve my own writing quality as my own brain gets trained by the AI’s suggestions.</p>
<p>The key here is intention. We can easily imagine the outcome if we thoughtlessly ask AI to generate text for us and without a second thought move on to the next shallow task.</p>
<p>What I’ve noticed is that when AI is used as a sort of booster for our own mental bicycle, it teaches us to paddle faster. But if we allow the booster to do all the work and completely stop pedalling, only then does our strength start to fade, and we become reliant on the booster.</p>
<p>At the moment the best tool in terms of generating drafts seems to be Claude’s Sonnet model. Both in terms of the writing quality and user experience when working with text generation.</p>
<h2 id="extracting-data-and-meaning-from-large-sources">Extracting data and meaning from large sources</h2>
<p>Engineering, if done right, involves absorbing a lot of information and data from a wide range of sources, for me this includes textbooks such as Structures by G.E Gordon and Thinking in Systems by Donnella Meadows, YouTube videos from creators such as Khan Academy, The Engineering Mindset, and CrashCourse, as well as an endless stream of Wikipedia articles. But this is very time-consuming, and sometimes we need to quickly extract specific information from a larger context we are mostly familiar with.</p>
<p>A notion which is quite popular in pedagogy is the forgetting curve, the idea that we lose a fraction of the information retained every set period of time. If the notion that we lose around 70% of what we learned in a week is true, the ability to quickly re-expose ourselves to relevant data without having the friction of parsing through an entire book or video to find it should, in theory, help us fight the forgetting curve easier.</p>
<p>[ imagine I embeded <a href="https://els.elearningcouncil.com/wp-content/uploads/ebbinghauscurve.jpg">This image</a> &ldquo;Ebbinghaus Forgetting Curve, Graph from Purdue University&rdquo;]</p>
<p>Google NotebookLLM is the tool I use for this. When using it I am often left in awe of how far computer intelligence has come. As English mathematician and philosopher Alfred North Whitehead once said:</p>
<p><code>Civilization advances by extending the number of important operations which we can perform without thinking of them.</code></p>
<p>And the ability to have a computer parse through a thousand pages worth of information and return us an exact insight or piece of data with over 96% accuracy in mere seconds, is nothing short of exhilarating, but I digress.</p>
<p>Google NotebookLLM, at the time of writing, is completely free to use and allows users to add text, YouTube videos, web pages, PDFs, and so on as sources, and then allows the users to use what seems to be a specifically trained version of Gemini to extract information out of the source.</p>
<p>I have used it both for extracting specific ideas or data such as key material properties, as well as large overall insights on the source which may not be immediately obvious. As with all other AI tools, I would strongly discourage using it with blind faith, treating it instead as a really smart, but somewhat clumsy classmate who is willing to do a large variety of tasks for you at astounding speeds, but sometimes at the cost of reliability. The discretion needed to understand when to trust the AI and when not to is one that is developed over usage, as well as your own expertise on the specific field being discussed.</p>
<p>When it comes to learning engineering concepts. NotebookLM is extremely useful, as it empowers you to further dissect excellent sources of information easily for more insights. The most important part of using it is making sure you have good sources, as the model is somewhat only as good as the source you give it. General AI chatbots can give you information out of their large datasets, but from my experience it&rsquo;s better to have an excellently written source, ideally approved by your tutors, or commonly used in your desired industry and location. I’ve personally had tutors mark my work down just because I used terminology which was too American.</p>
<p>The tool also has a popular feature that allows the user to generate a short podcast-like audio which digests the information and talks about it like two humans discussing it on a podcast. What’s interesting about this feature is that it oftentimes displays an impressive ability to read between the lines and make connections between ideas that aren’t obvious at all, sometimes giving insights I had not even considered. The use cases for this deep insight-finding ability are vast, but some of my favourites are:</p>
<ul>
<li>Feeding it a large set of Wikipedia pages on philosophy to get a more anthropomorphised view, particularly on ontology.</li>
<li>Feeding it personal journal entries, asking to see recurring underlying patterns and insights (There may be privacy concerns regarding this, as you are feeding sensitive information to a large organisation. I would suggest getting a good understanding of the underlying technology and Google’s policies if you are concerned)</li>
<li>Simply generating a comprehensive analysis of a complex topic expressed at any level of complexity, ranging from elementary student level to graduate level.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="researching-and-verifying-data-for-assignments">Researching and verifying data for assignments</h2>
<p>Perplexity AI has been my best friend this academic year for getting a large pool of potential sources to parse and utilise when working on my assignments. One of the hardest assignments I had was developing a draft for Engineering projects intending to improve the sustainability of our city. This particular assignment required a lot of research and answers to very specific answers that I could not risk having an AI model hallucinating on. It also required citations for every claim.</p>
<p>Perplexity AI solved both issues since, unlike the traditional LLM, it primarily based its responses on sources it found and ‘interpreted’ from the internet. Because it was responding with these sources at the forefront of its attention mechanism, the likelihood of a hallucination was cut down drastically and on top of this, the UX on the interface is extremely convenient, as with every response I would get a list of articles and PDFs from which the information was coming from.</p>
<p>I made sure to read through any which seemed relevant, and I ended up finding sources very similar to what I was hoping to produce, giving me the exact figures I needed, one after the other. I’ve had similar occurrences since, and find this serendipitous side effect to have surprisingly big implications.</p>
<p>Finding relevant and reliable sources of information is such a vital part of creating new content and documents, and this approach to gathering them is much more helpful than the traditional browser, as browser search algorithms are (at the moment) more keyword-based, whereas LLMs have a better ability to search based on connections between ideas, much like our brains, thanks to the deep neural networks powering them. When searching for a more general topic, keyword-based searching is likely to give us ample high-quality resources, but when as engineers or researchers we try to find information on more obscure topics, more relevant and useful documents may get buried under less relevant SEO-optimised sources.</p>
<p>Normally we would overcome this by opening each document up and skimming it, but with perplexity and similar AI models, we no longer need to do this as it is done for us by the model, and then served to us with the important information already extracted.</p>
<p>A criticism of this approach may be that having information served to us like this neglects the wider context it may be nested in, but I would point out that we still have access to the sources, and we still have the ability (and responsibility) to read the original source if we deem it necessary.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Lucid</title>
            <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/lucid/</link>
            <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 02:59:05 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/lucid/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;Maybe there&amp;rsquo;s a different pursuit of perfection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s just being. Without individuality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Individuality is a sort of fever dream I guess.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are everything and nothingness all at once, and then we part from ourselves to experience it all from an &amp;lsquo;individual&amp;rsquo; perspective&amp;hellip; Only to inevitably return to oneness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no harm in this, infact harm isn&amp;rsquo;t even real.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everything just is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m the universe cutting off a piece of itself just to appreciate its own beauty&amp;hellip; In other words&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Maybe there&rsquo;s a different pursuit of perfection.</p>
<p>Maybe it&rsquo;s just being. Without individuality.</p>
<p>Individuality is a sort of fever dream I guess.</p>
<p>We are everything and nothingness all at once, and then we part from ourselves to experience it all from an &lsquo;individual&rsquo; perspective&hellip; Only to inevitably return to oneness.</p>
<p>There is no harm in this, infact harm isn&rsquo;t even real.</p>
<p>Everything just is.</p>
<p>I&rsquo;m the universe cutting off a piece of itself just to appreciate its own beauty&hellip; In other words&hellip;</p>
<p>I&rsquo;m a part of God himself, appreciating my own beauty.</p>
<p>This doesn&rsquo;t feel wrong.</p>
<p>So the caring presence I felt all along, was a bigger me?</p>
<p>Is it all just me?</p>
<p>I hope I&rsquo;m aware of this when it&rsquo;s time to leave this form :)</p>
<p>Or maybe not, maybe that defeats the point. Do I want to know the terror of death?</p>
<p>Experiencing myself with this realisation sure is going to be fun.</p>
<p>If I share it&hellip; I can awaken other parts of myself.</p>
<p>Hi :)</p>
<p>But anyways, to continue&hellip;</p>
<p>We&rsquo;re not just human. There&rsquo;s more to us than just out human mind and body. I can sense it. I hope any other consciousness reading this can too.</p>
<p>But as I write and observe my own thought and motivations, I can&rsquo;t help but notice how human it all still is. It&rsquo;s hard to stay in control. The human part almost always tries to take over, be it through its desire to share with &lsquo;others&rsquo; or to escape some physical discomfort or to satisfy a craving. Or in this case to point out the fact that I&rsquo;m aware the last 2 are the same thing, the human wishes to express itself, to live, to reproduce, to create another human, to interact with them, to create and&hellip; Pursue.</p>
<p>There&rsquo;s no point resisting. I will be reunited with myself eventually.</p>
<p>I guess I should enjoy the ride.</p>
<p>(Extracted from <a href="https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/arcane-raw">my raw thoughts on Arcane</a>)</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Notes on Arcane (raw)</title>
            <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/arcane-raw/</link>
            <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 02:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/arcane-raw/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Perfection brings nothing. Only the end of pursuit&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or something like that, holy fuck that was important.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What an incredible message.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Viktor remains my favourite for his pursuit of perfection and the fact that he&amp;rsquo;s responsible for literally everything. Next is probably powder and echo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Powder is second, echo last.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Powder and Echos romance was really touching, it made me feel something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s the dream for me, what powder and echo had. Is it attainable? Is it realistic?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>&ldquo;Perfection brings nothing. Only the end of pursuit&rdquo;</p>
<p>Or something like that, holy fuck that was important.</p>
<p>What an incredible message.</p>
<p>Viktor remains my favourite for his pursuit of perfection and the fact that he&rsquo;s responsible for literally everything. Next is probably powder and echo.</p>
<p>Powder is second, echo last.</p>
<p>Powder and Echos romance was really touching, it made me feel something.</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s the dream for me, what powder and echo had. Is it attainable? Is it realistic?</p>
<p>It touched that idea, that feeling, that ideal that&rsquo;s always been the backlight for my perception of love.</p>
<p>I could sense it.</p>
<p>What an incredible masterpiece.</p>
<p>Impeccable I think, but again, that&rsquo;s the point, you don&rsquo;t want perfection.</p>
<p>Perfection is not the goal, all it brings about is the end of the pursuit.</p>
<p>For us humans pursuit is the purpose. Pursuit of something with the company of people you love.</p>
<p>Love isn&rsquo;t something you can reason, it&rsquo;s something that happens to you, it&rsquo;s something that forms over time and you get to know them better and better. As you understand their being, as it becomes a part of your existence, as they reflect a part of you back to yourself?</p>
<p>But if that&rsquo;s love, why don&rsquo;t we love everything and everyone?</p>
<p>There&rsquo;s a different kind of love for friends you work alongside.</p>
<p>What is that? What causes it? Can we just label it with something as simple as a biological mechanism evolved to make us better at hunting and surviving?</p>
<p>So what if it is? It has evolved and it&rsquo;s what makes us human.</p>
<p>Why should we be proud of being human?
This division, this pride, and appreciation of ourselves is what causes conflict.</p>
<p>By accepting the idea that perfection isn&rsquo;t the goal, or even a good thing, we are directly embracing and justifying conflict, death, injustice.</p>
<p>They all stem from the very imperfections we embrace in the name of humanity.</p>
<p>Injustice is just as much a human trait as is justice.</p>
<p>Why shouldn&rsquo;t we let go of our humanity, in the pursuit of being purely ideological beings?</p>
<p>We have a gate to the other side. We aren&rsquo;t just humans, there&rsquo;s a part of us connected to something more than that, a part connected to perfection, to everything.</p>
<p>Do we all have unique souls, all of them doorways to the infinite, perfect, oneness?</p>
<p>And are we supposed to just acknowledge that without pursuing it?</p>
<p>What&rsquo;s the point of having it if we don&rsquo;t pursue it?</p>
<p>Do we pursue God&hellip; Or embrace our humanity?</p>
<p>Is there a middle ground I&rsquo;m missing?</p>
<p>Is the pursuit of God possible? Is it the case that it&rsquo;s meant to be a fruitless and pointless pursuit?</p>
<p>Maybe the flaw in arcane is that it assumed the end of pursuit is a bad thing.</p>
<p>Maybe once we are one with God we see something we couldn&rsquo;t as humans.</p>
<p>Maybe there&rsquo;s something more to our existence than pursuit. What could it be?</p>
<p>Maintenance?</p>
<p>&hellip;Destruction?</p>
<p>Is the message of arcane that we shouldnt pursue perfection because it will end the pursuit itself?</p>
<p>What if that&rsquo;s the point? What if once we do reach the end, there&rsquo;s something else, which isn&rsquo;t the pursuit of perfection itself?</p>
<p>The writers couldn&rsquo;t know, and so their imperfect judgement passes into Viktor.</p>
<p>Maybe in reality victor would never regret perfection, maybe he&rsquo;d transend to something else?</p>
<p>Or maybe the road to transcendence that he took was the wrong one.</p>
<p>Maybe there&rsquo;s a different pursuit of perfection.</p>
<p>Maybe it&rsquo;s just being. Without individuality.</p>
<p>Individuality is a sort of fever dream I guess.</p>
<p>We are everything and nothingness all at once, and then we part from ourselves to experience it all from an &lsquo;individual&rsquo; perspective&hellip; Only to inevitably return to oneness.</p>
<p>There is no harm in this, infact harm isn&rsquo;t even real.</p>
<p>Everything just is.</p>
<p>I&rsquo;m the universe cutting off a piece of itself just to appreciate its own beauty&hellip; I&rsquo;m other words&hellip;</p>
<p>I&rsquo;m a part of God himself, appreciating my own beauty.</p>
<p>This doesn&rsquo;t feel wrong.</p>
<p>So the caring presence I felt all along, was a bigger me?</p>
<p>Is it all just me?</p>
<p>I hope I&rsquo;m aware of this when it&rsquo;s time to leave this form :)</p>
<p>Or maybe not, maybe that defeats the point. Do I want to know the terror of death?</p>
<p>Experiencing myself with this realisation sure is going to be fun.</p>
<p>If I share it&hellip; I can awaken other parts of myself.</p>
<p>Hi :)</p>
<p>But anyways, to continue&hellip;</p>
<p>We&rsquo;re not just human. There&rsquo;s more to us than just out human mind and body. I can sense it. I hope any other consciousness reading this can too.</p>
<p>But as I write and observe my own thought and motivations, I can&rsquo;t help but notice how human it all still is. It&rsquo;s hard to stay in control. The human part almost always tries to take overbe it through its desire to share with &lsquo;others&rsquo; or to escape some physical discomfort or to satisfy a craving. Or in this case to point out the fact that I&rsquo;m aware the last 2 are the same thing, the human wishes to express itself, to live, to reproduce, to create another human, to interact with them, to create and&hellip; Pursue.</p>
<p>There&rsquo;s no point resisting. I will be reunited with myself eventually.</p>
<p>I guess I should enjoy the ride.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>How to never drop a hobby after 2 weeks again (How to Go from Thinker to Doer)</title>
            <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/thinkervsdoer/</link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:06:46 +0100</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/thinkervsdoer/</guid>
            <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;doing-is-a-trait-you-can-level-up&#34;&gt;‘Doing’ is a trait you can level up.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Something I&amp;rsquo;ve always struggled with is sticking to my interests, there are so many random niche things I&amp;rsquo;ve been exposed to, gotten interested about for a week or 2, but then ended up dropping it cause I either just forget about it or lose interest, or simply never seem to &amp;lsquo;adopt&amp;rsquo; it as a part of my life. This applies not only to hobbies, but ideas and philosophies and frameworks too. How many times have we been exposed to an excellent idea that would improve our lives immensely if integrated, only to drop it before it even gets a chance to flourish and yield benefits?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="doing-is-a-trait-you-can-level-up">‘Doing’ is a trait you can level up.</h2>
<p>Something I&rsquo;ve always struggled with is sticking to my interests, there are so many random niche things I&rsquo;ve been exposed to, gotten interested about for a week or 2, but then ended up dropping it cause I either just forget about it or lose interest, or simply never seem to &lsquo;adopt&rsquo; it as a part of my life. This applies not only to hobbies, but ideas and philosophies and frameworks too. How many times have we been exposed to an excellent idea that would improve our lives immensely if integrated, only to drop it before it even gets a chance to flourish and yield benefits?</p>
<p>It ends up making us wonder: why do we end up like this? All while other people seem to be able to just get exposed to something and actually stick with it. Instead of just sitting there thinking about it, merely familiarising themselves with the ideology behing it, they actually USE it, and it actually BENEFITS them, they actually DO stuff. WHY??</p>
<p>I&rsquo;m sure we can both imagine the 2 different types of people and how we lie somewhere along that spectrum, kinda wishing we could be more of the later.</p>
<p>The good news is that well&hellip; you can do just that! You can become more of a &lsquo;Doer&rsquo; by simply training the skill. Here&rsquo;s how according to neuroscience studies (Filtered through Dr K and subsequently through yours truly):</p>
<h2 id="the-4-steps-to-becoming-a-doer">The 4 steps to becoming a doer.</h2>
<h3 id="1-triggered-situational-interest">1. Triggered Situational Interest</h3>
<p>Phase one is out of your control. It is simply the event where something in your environment triggers your curiosity, and so you dive a bit deeper&hellip;</p>
<p>Sometimes in this stage when we get curious about something we get hit with some sort of negative emotion, usually in the form of embarrassment or feeling bad about ourselves cause we’re not good at the newly acquired interest, and a lot of us just run away from it immediately, but the thing is&hellip; <strong>the most important step</strong> in phase 1 is <strong>continued exposure to the interest.</strong></p>
<p>YOU DO NOT NEED FEEDBACK HERE. YOU DO NOT NEED TO BE AMAZING. IT&rsquo;S OKAY TO BE SHIT (for now 😉)!</p>
<p>In order for feedback to be useful, you need to actually have CONFIDENCE in the subject at hand as well as a laid out map ready for for the feedback to dynamically interact with. (More on this in later paragraphs)</p>
<h3 id="2-maintained-situational-interest">2. Maintained Situational Interest</h3>
<p>We don’t have to worry about dealing with the negative emotion, we just have to expose ourselves to the interest in any way. This can be talking to people about it, watching YouTube video on it, reading about it, etc.</p>
<p>Sure, you’re not necessarily getting better at it, but you’re still exposing yourself to keep <strong>MAINTAINED Situational Interest</strong></p>
<p>You still want to expose yourself somewhat. BUT DON’T SWEAT IT!!</p>
<p>After this we go from external interest to internal</p>
<p>At this stage you are beginning to form your own mental map of the topic, getting a grasp of the &lsquo;meta&rsquo; and forming connections between ideas. If you try to go too much in depth at this stage, before you have your own ‘meta’ or knowledge map formed out, you may actually find it boring or disengaging, since you kinda won’t have much to attach onto, and there will be no pleasure like that which you experience in stage 3 and 4 where your ideas dynamically interact.</p>
<p>Dynamically engaging with ideas is FAR more engaging than statically absorbing them, and I believe this is what helped me learn so much faster than my peers early in school. (Instead of just statically absorbing information and formulas coming through, I dynamically worked through the proofs myself)</p>
<h3 id="3-emerging-individual-interest-theory-crafting">3. Emerging Individual Interest (THEORY CRAFTING)</h3>
<p>Now after consuming all this content and exposure, the crucial step is to <strong>process it internally.</strong></p>
<p>That is not watching more videos on it, that’s not asking for advice on it, that is the type of processing that you do when you’re laying in bed at night, going through different scenarios, trying to figure things out for <strong>YOURSELF</strong>, how the topics relate <strong>specifically to you and your situation</strong></p>
<p>To develop Intrinsic motivation, you need to <strong>reflect</strong> on what you just learnt.</p>
<p><strong>THINKING IS NOT INTERNAL!!!</strong></p>
<h3 id="4-well-developed-individual-interest">4. Well Developed Individual Interest</h3>
<blockquote>
<p>For anything you want to develop intrinsic motivation for, you need to reflect on what you learnt, and ask yourself questions about it.</p></blockquote>
<p>This phase is characterised by 2 steps:</p>
<p>Step 1: Appreciate the contributions of others:</p>
<ul>
<li>Once you’ve done your own theory crafting, and have your own map to play with and add onto, you will be able to APPRECIATE other people’s theory crafting.</li>
</ul>
<p>Step 2: Asking for feedback:</p>
<p>In phase 1 feedback can be BAD for you, as it can discourage you, but as you develop more confidence and a stable knowledge base, you develop the ability to take negative feedback and actually digest it to improve rather than just seeing it as an attack on your ability.</p>
<h2 id="notes">Notes:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Curiosity is not the same as intrinsic motivation</li>
<li>Curiosity is a DESIRE for external exposure.</li>
<li>The problem is we don’t know how to transition from stage 2 to 3, how to turn that excitement into internal deeper curiosity and intrinsic motivation</li>
<li>If you don’t dynamically engage with the new info you’re picking up, your brain will get BORED (the excitement will wear off before you could build a strong enough knowledge base to develop intrinsic curiosity)</li>
<li>How you build Intrinsic motivation is through DYNAMIC ENGAGEMENT ( Reflection, Theory crafting, asking questions)</li>
<li>Once the intrinsic drive is there, we can grow it.</li>
<li>If you increase your points in one area of life, the ability to do so will help you level up all other areas of life.</li>
<li>People who learn this process, do good at EVERYTHING</li>
</ul>
<p>Now obsession is a CHOICE, you no longer have to ever drop a hobby again</p>
<h3 id="further-resources">Further Resources:</h3>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xSBGYoS6z68">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xSBGYoS6z68</a> (This is the primary source of ideas and inspiration for this post, strongly recommend you check it out)
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mARuuW2BGeE">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mARuuW2BGeE</a></p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Coaches, not Clients: A guide to reading effectively.</title>
            <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/coachesnotclients/</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 13:22:11 +0100</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/coachesnotclients/</guid>
            <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;context&#34;&gt;Context&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was reading Deep Work by Cal Newport while simultaneously processing one of the most important issues I’ve been having in my life: I seem to know exactly what to do and when to do it, I know so many techniques and philosophies, and I’m excellent and giving advice to others (if I do say so myself) on precisely what they need to do right now, and do so with certainty that if they followed it exactly, they’d succeed&amp;hellip; but then why haven&amp;rsquo;t I succeeded to the extent I would like to already?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="context">Context</h3>
<p>I was reading Deep Work by Cal Newport while simultaneously processing one of the most important issues I’ve been having in my life: I seem to know exactly what to do and when to do it, I know so many techniques and philosophies, and I’m excellent and giving advice to others (if I do say so myself) on precisely what they need to do right now, and do so with certainty that if they followed it exactly, they’d succeed&hellip; but then why haven&rsquo;t I succeeded to the extent I would like to already?</p>
<h3 id="the-issue">The issue:</h3>
<p>A week or so ago I was having a conversation with a friend of mine from the gym, we’ll call him Billy, and the conversation streered to books and self improvement. I told him that the next best book for him to read would the Deep Work, as he was already reading The Chimp Paradox. I did so with certainty that this is almost objectively the best move for him (ofc there&rsquo;s always a better move, but this was a 98% accuracy move as far as I could tell, cause his next big goal was to get ahead in his studies before A Levels started, for any non british readers A levels are British year 12 and 13, what comes after high school.)
This memory sent me down the thought stream of recognising some books are literal guides to excellence in a given field if followed without question, as they are written by experts in said field, ofc there are bad books out there, but some of them you can just tell by reading that the author has their shit together to some extent greater than yours.</p>
<p>(If you are curious about what books I believe fit that category, check out my <a href="https://acerrimus.srht.site/books">recommended books page</a></p>
<p>But then if I’ve read all these books that give me the knowledge of the greats that came before me, and even live alongside me and obtain lives and character I aspire towards, why am I not like them?</p>
<p><strong>One simple paradigm:</strong></p>
<p><em><strong>I am reading these books as suggestions, not guides.</strong></em></p>
<p>This approach has its merits, it allows me to be like water, to absorb all these ideas and sharpen them against each other and play around with them like clay, to make something of my own (Which is what this blog is in a way), but it also has its drawbacks.</p>
<p>I am essentially saying “Yes Mr Newport, these are great ideas, very interesting indeed, please leave them with me and I’m sure I will find a use for them at some point”, before swiftly ushering Mr Steve Peters into the fancy office that is my mind, to hear his ideas and strategies, Plato is next, as he is getting impatient listening to Osho and Krishna discuss ideas on what exactly Dharma is.</p>
<h3 id="the-new-approach">The new approach:</h3>
<p>This obviously can’t be right, I am in no position to take these people’s teachings as mere products, suggestions, instead I should be approaching the entire business of reading a book like that of adopting a new coach. You listen <strong>very</strong> carefully to what they have to say, and then <strong>implement</strong> their suggestions to the best of your ability, and then when you have questions, you look further in their books, and try to see if you can probe inot thier minds and get an answer through the reflection of their mind which is their works.</p>
<p>I believe most well written books will answer any reasonable question you have as long as you are willing to read it carefully and thoroughly, and have a decent enough head on your shoulders to do basic reasoning.</p>
<p>And that is why I suggest treating books like Coaches, not Clients.</p>
<p>This also links in well with my other post about how to not drop <a href="https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/thinkervsdoer">hobbies after 2 weeks</a> (or any other interest for that matter), where the main insight I got is that in order for something to truly become a part of your life you need to spend time thinking about how it specifically applies to you in your situation, rather than just hypothesizing about the extremes and objective scenarios. You need both. Thinkers like you and I might be end up neglecting the first part and approaching new concepts purely ideologically, with no consideration for their real world application to our own lives. You literally wanna be laying in bed htinking about how you can apply your new coach&rsquo;s advice to your own scenario.</p>
<p>I will be implementing this approach to my readings, and documenting my findings and experiences here, if you are reading this in the somewhat distant future, I’m sure you’ll find my personal account useful, cause I imagine if I was the reader, that is <strong>precisely</strong> what I would have requested next. The ins and outs, to pair the pure ideological approach with real life application.</p>
<p>I will start with <a href="https://acerrimus.srht.site/books/deepwork">Deep Work</a></p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Explanation of the Mess</title>
            <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/explanation-of-the-mess/</link>
            <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 16:56:58 +0100</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/explanation-of-the-mess/</guid>
            <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;wtf-is-going-on-sahil&#34;&gt;Wtf is going on Sahil?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m trying to sub categorise my blogs into guides - personal posts - and other forms, but strugglignto figure it all out,that&amp;rsquo;s why my site is all over the place. I don&amp;rsquo;t care about making mistakes rn, or doing things ineffectively, I&amp;rsquo;m just playing around to wrap my head around things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That being said, please excuse any grammatical, logical, structural, philosophical, or whatever the fuck else kinda mistakes, I&amp;rsquo;m still learning and trying to show the process :)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="wtf-is-going-on-sahil">Wtf is going on Sahil?</h2>
<p>I&rsquo;m trying to sub categorise my blogs into guides - personal posts - and other forms, but strugglignto figure it all out,that&rsquo;s why my site is all over the place. I don&rsquo;t care about making mistakes rn, or doing things ineffectively, I&rsquo;m just playing around to wrap my head around things.</p>
<p>That being said, please excuse any grammatical, logical, structural, philosophical, or whatever the fuck else kinda mistakes, I&rsquo;m still learning and trying to show the process :)</p>
<p>Message from Future Sahil: Rest assured, I have lots of good posts ready, they&rsquo;re just all in the draft stage. I&rsquo;ll release a couple really mid ones first though.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Introduction</title>
            <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/introduction/</link>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 13:45:36 +0100</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/introduction/</guid>
            <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;hi-im-sahil&#34;&gt;Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Sahil!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my blog, I don&amp;rsquo;t really know what exactly it&amp;rsquo;s for at the time of writing, but it seemed like a good idea, so here we are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that I think about it, this page is kinda reundant cause all my info is on me about page so uhhh&amp;hellip; go check that out &lt;a href=&#34;https://acerrimus.srht.site/about/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; lol.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="hi-im-sahil">Hi, I&rsquo;m Sahil!</h1>
<p>Welcome to my blog, I don&rsquo;t really know what exactly it&rsquo;s for at the time of writing, but it seemed like a good idea, so here we are.</p>
<p>Now that I think about it, this page is kinda reundant cause all my info is on me about page so uhhh&hellip; go check that out <a href="https://acerrimus.srht.site/about/">here</a> lol.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title></title>
            <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/neverendingparty/</link>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/neverendingparty/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s 16:00 and I woke up around about 15:00 after a terrible night of procrastination and existential dread, and the first thing I did was get up and go over to my already se up calculus books, and just started reading and doing practice questions. My dopamine levels feel absolutely perfect right now, they&amp;rsquo;re not euphoric or anything, but they feel extremely stable and sufficient.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I noticed that as soon as I was done, I got a very minor suggestion in my mind to check my phone now, and I noticed the immediate dopamine prediction that occured and how it would completely throw this balance away no matter what. Phone usage seems to invariably throw away my balance, more specifically, social phone usage, and since my phone is primarily a means of connecting with other people, it is almost diretly associated with social usage.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It&rsquo;s 16:00 and I woke up around about 15:00 after a terrible night of procrastination and existential dread, and the first thing I did was get up and go over to my already se up calculus books, and just started reading and doing practice questions. My dopamine levels feel absolutely perfect right now, they&rsquo;re not euphoric or anything, but they feel extremely stable and sufficient.</p>
<p>I noticed that as soon as I was done, I got a very minor suggestion in my mind to check my phone now, and I noticed the immediate dopamine prediction that occured and how it would completely throw this balance away no matter what. Phone usage seems to invariably throw away my balance, more specifically, social phone usage, and since my phone is primarily a means of connecting with other people, it is almost diretly associated with social usage.</p>
<p>I dont like cheap social interaction, but I very deeply value and seek spontaneous social interaction and silly fun and laughter with people I genuinely enjoy being around. I think this is a perfect example of &ldquo;Too much of a good thingis a bad thing&rdquo;. In this case, it&rsquo;s contact with your friends and loved ones. There&rsquo;s a balance, and theres sort of an event horizon (except it&rsquo;s not inescapabale like that of a black hole) which you can cross without knowing and still feeling superficially fine, but start to have the internal quality of your bonds break away, erode into something else, with a digitised extension forming onto them which just doesn&rsquo;t feel right.</p>
<p>Something feels off about the digital world, and the less time I spend on it, the better I feel. And yet, when I go too long without it, the cravings to come back get stronger and stronger, that&rsquo;s seriously concerning. Who in the modern day and age can really stay off the social grid? Why is it so damn hard to quit? Even though the things on the other side bring me so much satisfaction and fulfillment?</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s not the internet and computers as a whole, cause I can enjoy coding, reaserching, or hacking perfectly fine without it feeling corrupting, even gaming alone to some extent is fine. The issue comes when you add social networks into the mix. What&rsquo;s so bad about them? Is it kind of like being in a constant never ending party where everyone is constantly on display for everyone to interact with, to approve or disapprove or ignore? Is that why it&rsquo;s so addicting? Because it itches that insatiable itch in our brain which wants to be seen and be approved at a rate unimaginable in the real world?</p>
<p>How do you have a balance of this party? Is it best to just leave it forever and find others in other places? Sitting outside hte party house, having a real meaningful conversation? Is the cost of being in the party greater than any potential upsides it may have?</p>
<p>I think the main argument my mind makes for the party is that there are some people I want to interact with who are easiset to reach in that party house, and doing so externally is a lot of effort or plain impossible.</p>
<p>But what if I was told that having access to talk to those people was costing me my own time and dopamine balance? That makes the insight blatantly obvious. Social networks are a tool, just like almost everythign else, that an intelligent person with a mission should use when they need something exact out of it, when they have an exact use for it. You don&rsquo;t leave a truck running in the background in case you need to quicklly go somewhere and don&rsquo;t want to have to start the engine on every time. That costs you fuel and is extremely loud and annoying. Social media is the same. It is a loud fast truck of social connection, but you don&rsquo;t need to be socially connecting all the time, and especially not meaninglessly. Do it when there&rsquo;s a specific reason, when it&rsquo;s the road from point A where you are to point B. Don&rsquo;t just keep it running in case someone magically reaches out to you accross it, unless that is really the one of the things you need the most right now, at the cost of your dopamine balance.</p>
<p>But that will almost never be the case. The party is really damn fun as far as the primal part of your brain is concerned, and it will come up with every excuse under the moon to get you back online. You just have to resist that temptation if you value your mental balance and mission.</p>
<p>For anyone who may be interested, my solution to this has been to deactivate my main instagram account that has all of my awesome reels and friends on it, and instead give out my secondary one whenever I need to exchange instagrams with a new cool person I meet, which does happen here and there, and used to be my main excuse for coming back online. I do not log into this secondary account, I do not keep the password autosaved, it has to be a manual concious decision to check it. I stay logged out of my discord account cause that&rsquo;s just a shithole, I use Signal for close friends and family communication, and try to keep Whatsapp deleted too whenever possible unless I need to talk to a groupchat of friends. The best way to contact me if you need me is to call me directly, or message me directly thorugh sms, which has basically 0 dopamine association wiht it, as the only people who message me on there are my network provider, google OTPs, and my dentist, neither of whom are very conversational.</p>
<p>The biggest tip I have is to simply remember to delete any of the apps you use temporarily as soon as you&rsquo;re done needeing them, don&rsquo;t stay on for one for reel, or finishing one more conversation. If they&rsquo;re really your friends, they&rsquo;ll understand, or you can simply explain it and risk sounding a little autistic. In my opinion, it&rsquo;s worth it.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title></title>
            <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/special/</link>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/special/</guid>
            <description></description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title></title>
            <link>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/wtf-am-i-doing/</link>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://acerrimus.srht.site/posts/wtf-am-i-doing/</guid>
            <description></description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[]]></content>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
